- It looks absolutely terrible.
- Yes, it looks terrible.
Here it is.
Axel will let go straight down through the floor up there ...
... and go down here, down through this hole.
It does not look wise because it is open.
It is like no capsule.
♪ (eerie music) ♪
Oh five, then ...
Oh God.
Yes, I'm ready.
Oh, five.
(Axel screams)
Wooo!
- How was it?
- God, then ... no but then, that was so uncomfortable.
It was just so much water ... everywhere.
I got so much cold soup.
But it goes so fast.
Two seconds!
- just two seconds?
- Yes!
They said it.
Two seconds ride.
- Oh my God.
- 60 km/h.
It is the "drop" itself as well, when the door opens, that's when you just ... (WAAH!)
- Yes, you swept past us.
- Yes.
- Here, you can take Laura.
- Yes, I can take Laura.
Hello friend.
She did not understand at all what was happening.
Dad just flew past and screamed.
Wooo!
This is the ride!
Woho!
(Alma) Woho!
(All three tjar)
Yabba Dabba Doo!
(Harry) "Look Out!"
(Beware!)
- (Joanna) Was it fun?
- Yes!
Yabba Dabba Doo!
Yahooo!
So, that was sow-
- Fun!
- ... fun!
- In chorus!
It was swine fun.
- Yes, it really was.
- Check out what beautiful ... No, you don't see the light.
- We see the light.
It's a little pink and orange over there.
It is half past eleven in the evening ... and we have energy!